{"SurveyEntry":{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","SurveyName":"Crystal Census Final - US","SurveyDescription":null,"SurveyOwnerID":"UR_CjpOkiX50dY8GTn","SurveyBrandID":"corexmsttsns4342x2kg","DivisionID":null,"SurveyLanguage":"EN","SurveyActiveResponseSet":"RS_9N3B3pHlHtMt4SG","SurveyStatus":"Active","SurveyStartDate":"0000-00-00 00:00:00","SurveyExpirationDate":"0000-00-00 00:00:00","SurveyCreationDate":"2021-01-14 22:05:58","CreatorID":"UR_CjpOkiX50dY8GTn","LastModified":"2021-01-20 11:09:27","LastAccessed":"0000-00-00 00:00:00","LastActivated":"2021-01-14 22:06:58","Deleted":null},"SurveyElements":[{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"BL","PrimaryAttribute":"Survey Blocks","SecondaryAttribute":null,"TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":[{"Type":"Default","Description":"Default Question Block","ID":"BL_ewWGiCQhtfxUAG9","BlockElements":[{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID10"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID32"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID33"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID1"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID5"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID6"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID34"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID35"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID14"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID37"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID18"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID38"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID21"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID39"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID40"},{"Type":"Page Break"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID43"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID22"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID23"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID24"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID25"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID26"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID27"}]},{"Type":"Trash","Description":"Trash \/ Unused Questions","ID":"BL_6s3oWJ2CcASe5Pn","BlockElements":[{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID12"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID16"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID17"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID19"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID15"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID41"},{"Type":"Question","QuestionID":"QID42"}],"Options":{"BlockLocking":"false","RandomizeQuestions":"false","BlockVisibility":"Collapsed"}}]},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"FL","PrimaryAttribute":"Survey Flow","SecondaryAttribute":null,"TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"Type":"Root","FlowID":"FL_1","Flow":[{"Type":"Block","ID":"BL_ewWGiCQhtfxUAG9","FlowID":"FL_2","Autofill":[]}],"Properties":{"Count":2,"RemovedFieldsets":[]}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"RS","PrimaryAttribute":"RS_9N3B3pHlHtMt4SG","SecondaryAttribute":null,"TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":null},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SO","PrimaryAttribute":"Survey Options","SecondaryAttribute":null,"TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"BackButton":"true","SaveAndContinue":"true","SurveyProtection":"PublicSurvey","BallotBoxStuffingPrevention":"true","NoIndex":"Yes","SecureResponseFiles":"true","SurveyExpiration":null,"SurveyTermination":"DisplayMessage","Header":"","Footer":"","ProgressBarDisplay":"NoText","PartialData":"+2 days","ValidationMessage":null,"PreviousButton":" \u2190 ","NextButton":"Submit Survey","SurveyTitle":"Online Survey Software | Qualtrics Survey Solutions","SkinLibrary":"corexmsttsns4342x2kg","SkinType":"templated","Skin":{"brandingId":null,"templateId":"*modern","overrides":{"progressBar":{"position":"bottom"},"questionText":{"size":"19px"},"answerText":{"size":"15px"},"logo":{"url":"https:\/\/corexmsttsns4342x2kg.qualtrics.com\/CP\/Graphic.php?IM=IM_9BuonSMCd1bICot"}}},"NewScoring":1,"EOSMessage":"MS_3f0UqizsTEbt6mi","ShowExportTags":"false","CollectGeoLocation":"false","SurveyMetaDescription":"The most powerful, simple and trusted way to gather experience data. Start your journey to experience management and try a free account today.","PasswordProtection":"No","AnonymizeResponse":"Yes","Password":"","RefererCheck":"No","RefererURL":"http:\/\/","UseCustomSurveyLinkCompletedMessage":null,"SurveyLinkCompletedMessage":"","SurveyLinkCompletedMessageLibrary":"","ResponseSummary":"No","EOSMessageLibrary":"UR_CjpOkiX50dY8GTn","EOSRedirectURL":"https:\/\/","EmailThankYou":"false","ThankYouEmailMessageLibrary":null,"ThankYouEmailMessage":null,"ValidateMessage":"false","ValidationMessageLibrary":null,"InactiveSurvey":"DefaultMessage","PartialDeletion":null,"PartialDataCloseAfter":"LastActivity","ActiveResponseSet":null,"InactiveMessageLibrary":"","InactiveMessage":"","AvailableLanguages":{"EN":[]},"CustomStyles":[],"Autoadvance":"true","AutoadvanceHideButton":"true","nextButtonLid":"","nextButtonMid":"","ProtectSelectionIds":true,"SurveyName":"Crystal Census Final - US"}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SCO","PrimaryAttribute":"Scoring","SecondaryAttribute":null,"TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"ScoringCategories":[],"ScoringCategoryGroups":[],"ScoringSummaryCategory":null,"ScoringSummaryAfterQuestions":0,"ScoringSummaryAfterSurvey":0,"DefaultScoringCategory":null,"AutoScoringCategory":null}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"PROJ","PrimaryAttribute":"CORE","SecondaryAttribute":null,"TertiaryAttribute":"1.1.0","Payload":{"ProjectCategory":"CORE","SchemaVersion":"1.1.0"}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"STAT","PrimaryAttribute":"Survey Statistics","SecondaryAttribute":null,"TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"MobileCompatible":true,"ID":"Survey Statistics"}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"QC","PrimaryAttribute":"Survey Question Count","SecondaryAttribute":"43","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":null},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID38","SecondaryAttribute":"Academic Interests: Classes","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Academic Interests: Classes","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q12","QuestionType":"Matrix","Selector":"Likert","SubSelector":"SingleAnswer","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","TextPosition":"inline","ChoiceColumnWidth":25,"RepeatHeaders":"none","WhiteSpace":"OFF","MobileFirst":true},"QuestionDescription":"Academic Interests: Classes","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Which academic subject assigns the most homework?"},"2":{"Display":"For which department does Crystal need more elective courses?"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":9,"Answers":{"1":{"Display":"Math"},"2":{"Display":"Science"},"3":{"Display":"History"},"4":{"Display":"English"},"5":{"Display":"Language"},"6":{"Display":"Arts"},"7":{"Display":"CADS"}},"AnswerOrder":["1","2","3","4","5","6","7"],"ChoiceDataExportTags":false,"QuestionID":"QID38","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID21","SecondaryAttribute":"Are there any elective courses you would like Crystal to offer in the future?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"
<span id=\"docs-internal-guid-f6ba22af-7fff-1927-8808-6d695a329402\"><span
style=\"font-size: 11pt; font-family: Arial; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); background-color: transparent; font-variant-numeric: normal; font-variant-east-asian: normal; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;\">Are there any elective courses you would like Crystal to offer in the future?<\/span><\/span>","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q13","QuestionID":"QID21","QuestionType":"TE","Selector":"SL","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false},"Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"Are there any elective courses you would like Crystal to offer in the future?","Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"OFF","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":8,"NextAnswerId":1,"SearchSource":{"AllowFreeResponse":"false"}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID41","SecondaryAttribute":"Click to write the question text","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Click to write the question text","DataExportTag":"Q29","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"Click to write the question text","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Click to write Choice 1"},"2":{"Display":"Click to write Choice 2"},"3":{"Display":"Click to write Choice 3"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"OFF","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID41"}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID42","SecondaryAttribute":"Click to write the question text","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Click to write the question text","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q30","QuestionType":"DB","Selector":"TB","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"Click to write the question text","ChoiceOrder":[],"Validation":{"Settings":{"Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID42"}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID17","SecondaryAttribute":"Crystal has enough extracurricular activities related to your academic interests\/ambitions.","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Crystal has enough extracurricular activities related to your academic interests\/ambitions.","DataExportTag":"Q17","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","Autoscale":{"YScale":{"Name":"agreeDisagree","Type":"likert","Reverse":false}}},"QuestionDescription":"Crystal has enough extracurricular activities related to your academic interests\/ambitions.","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Strongly agree"},"2":{"Display":"Somewhat agree"},"3":{"Display":"Neither agree nor disagree"},"4":{"Display":"Somewhat disagree"},"5":{"Display":"Strongly disagree"}},"ChoiceOrder":[1,2,3,4,5],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":6,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID17","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID43","SecondaryAttribute":"Demographics","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Demographics","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q16","QuestionType":"DB","Selector":"TB","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"Demographics","ChoiceOrder":[],"Validation":{"Settings":{"Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID43","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID37","SecondaryAttribute":"Do you feel that Crystal has enough extracurricular activities related to your academic interests?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Do you feel that Crystal has enough extracurricular activities related to your academic interests?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q10","QuestionType":"Slider","Selector":"HSLIDER","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","CSSliderMin":1,"CSSliderMax":5,"GridLines":4,"SnapToGrid":false,"NumDecimals":"0","ShowValue":true,"CustomStart":false,"NotApplicable":false,"MobileFirst":true},"QuestionDescription":"Do you feel that Crystal has enough extracurricular activities related to your academic interests?","Choices":{"3":{"Display":"&nbsp;"}},"ChoiceOrder":["3"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":3,"Labels":{"1":{"Display":"Not Enough"},"2":{"Display":"Enough"}},"QuestionID":"QID37","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID10","SecondaryAttribute":"During Spirit Weeks, how many days do you typically participate?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"During Spirit Weeks, how many days do you typically participate?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q1","QuestionType":"Slider","Selector":"HSLIDER","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","CSSliderMin":0,"CSSliderMax":5,"GridLines":5,"SnapToGrid":true,"NumDecimals":"0","ShowValue":false,"CustomStart":true,"NotApplicable":false,"MobileFirst":true,"SliderStartPositions":{"1":0}},"QuestionDescription":"During Spirit Weeks, how many days do you typically participate?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"&nbsp;"}},"ChoiceOrder":[1],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":10,"Labels":[],"QuestionID":"QID10","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false},"Answers":{"1":{"Display":0},"2":{"Display":1},"3":{"Display":2},"4":{"Display":3},"5":{"Display":4},"6":{"Display":5}}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID19","SecondaryAttribute":"For what department does Crystal need more elective courses?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"For what department does Crystal need more elective courses?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q19","QuestionID":"QID19","QuestionType":"RO","Selector":"DND","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"For what department does Crystal need more elective courses?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Math"},"2":{"Display":"Science"},"3":{"Display":"History"},"4":{"Display":"English"},"5":{"Display":"Language"},"6":{"Display":"Arts"},"7":{"Display":"CADS"}},"ChoiceOrder":[1,2,3,4,5,6,7],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":8,"NextAnswerId":1,"DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID27","SecondaryAttribute":"How many people do you live with?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"How many people do you live with?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q22","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"How many people do you live with?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"0"},"2":{"Display":"1"},"4":{"Display":"2"},"5":{"Display":"3"},"6":{"Display":"4"},"7":{"Display":"5"},"8":{"Display":"6"},"10":{"Display":"7"},"11":{"Display":"8+"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","4","5","6","7","8","10","11"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":13,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID27","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID40","SecondaryAttribute":"If yes to the previous, which departments would you most like to collaborate? (Select 2-3)","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"<span
id=\"docs-internal-guid-72e0f561-7fff-6edd-0455-f6eaf7d5d45c\"><span
style=\"background-color: transparent; font-variant-numeric: normal; font-variant-east-asian: normal; vertical-align: baseline;\">I<\/span><span
style=\"font-size: 11pt; font-family: Arial; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); background-color: transparent; font-variant-numeric: normal; font-variant-east-asian: normal; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;\">f yes to the previous, which departments would you most like to collaborate? (Select 2-3)<\/span><\/span>","DataExportTag":"Q15","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"MAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"If yes to the previous, which departments would you most like to collaborate? (Select 2-3)","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Math"},"2":{"Display":"Science"},"3":{"Display":"History"},"4":{"Display":"English"},"5":{"Display":"Language"},"6":{"Display":"Arts"},"7":{"Display":"CADS"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4","5","6","7"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"OFF","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":8,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID40","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID5","SecondaryAttribute":"Time Audit: Academics","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Time Audit: Academics","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q5","QuestionID":"QID5","QuestionType":"Matrix","Selector":"Likert","SubSelector":"SingleAnswer","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false},"Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","TextPosition":"inline","ChoiceColumnWidth":25,"RepeatHeaders":"none","WhiteSpace":"OFF","MobileFirst":true},"QuestionDescription":"Time Audit: Academics","Choices":{"2":{"Display":"How many hours do you spend on homework on a given weekday?"},"8":{"Display":"How many hours do you spend on homework on a given weekend (both days combined)?"}},"ChoiceOrder":[2,"8"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":9,"NextAnswerId":7,"Answers":{"1":{"Display":"1"},"2":{"Display":"2"},"3":{"Display":"3"},"4":{"Display":"4"},"5":{"Display":"5"},"6":{"Display":"6+"}},"AnswerOrder":["1","2","3","4","5","6"],"ChoiceDataExportTags":false}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID1","SecondaryAttribute":"Time Audit: Events and Extracurriculars","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Time Audit: Events and Extracurriculars","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q4","QuestionID":"QID1","QuestionType":"Matrix","Selector":"Likert","SubSelector":"SingleAnswer","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false},"Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","TextPosition":"inline","ChoiceColumnWidth":25,"RepeatHeaders":"none","WhiteSpace":"OFF","MobileFirst":true},"QuestionDescription":"Time Audit: Events and Extracurriculars","Choices":{"7":{"Display":"How many Crystal events do you attend per semester? (i.e., sports games, homecoming, dance, lunar banquet)"},"15":{"Display":"How many hours per week do you spend participating in Crystal extracurriculars?"},"16":{"Display":"How many hours per week do you spend participating in non-Crystal extracurriculars?"},"17":{"Display":"How many hours per week do you spend volunteering and\/or doing community service?"}},"ChoiceOrder":["7","15","16","17"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":19,"NextAnswerId":10,"Answers":{"1":{"Display":"1"},"2":{"Display":"2"},"3":{"Display":"3"},"4":{"Display":"4"},"5":{"Display":"5"},"6":{"Display":"6"},"7":{"Display":"7"},"8":{"Display":"8"},"9":{"Display":"9+"}},"AnswerOrder":["1","2","3","4","5","6","7","8","9"],"ChoiceDataExportTags":false}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID6","SecondaryAttribute":"Time Audit: Sleep","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Time Audit: Sleep","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q6","QuestionID":"QID6","QuestionType":"Matrix","Selector":"Likert","SubSelector":"SingleAnswer","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false},"Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","TextPosition":"inline","ChoiceColumnWidth":25,"RepeatHeaders":"none","WhiteSpace":"OFF","MobileFirst":true},"QuestionDescription":"Time Audit: Sleep","Choices":{"5":{"Display":"How many hours of sleep do you get on a typical weekday?"},"9":{"Display":"How many hours of sleep do you get on a typical weekend?"}},"ChoiceOrder":["5","9"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":10,"NextAnswerId":7,"Answers":{"1":{"Display":"5 or Less"},"2":{"Display":"6"},"3":{"Display":"7"},"4":{"Display":"8"},"5":{"Display":"9"},"6":{"Display":"10 or More"}},"AnswerOrder":["1","2","3","4","5","6"],"ChoiceDataExportTags":false}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID15","SecondaryAttribute":"What does Crystal do that causes you to get less sleep than usual?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What does Crystal do that causes you to get less sleep than usual?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q15","QuestionID":"QID15","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"MAVR","SubSelector":"TX","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false},"Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What does Crystal do that causes you to get less sleep than usual?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Crunch Weeks"},"2":{"Display":"Too Much Homework"},"3":{"Display":"Sports"},"4":{"Display":"Theater Productions"}},"ChoiceOrder":[1,2,3,4],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"OFF","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":5,"NextAnswerId":1}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID14","SecondaryAttribute":"What does Crystal do that causes you to get more sleep than usual? (Drag to rank)","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What does Crystal do that causes you to get more sleep than usual? (Drag to rank)","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q9","QuestionType":"RO","Selector":"DND","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What does Crystal do that causes you to get more sleep than usual? (Drag to rank)","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"No Homework Weekends"},"2":{"Display":"Late Starts"},"3":{"Display":"Two Major Assessment Limit Per Day"},"4":{"Display":"Time Limits on Homework Length"},"5":{"Display":"ERFs"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4","5"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":6,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID14","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID33","SecondaryAttribute":"What does your free-time vs. obligations balance look like?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What does your free-time vs. obligations balance look like?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q3","QuestionType":"Slider","Selector":"HSLIDER","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","CSSliderMin":0,"CSSliderMax":10,"GridLines":10,"SnapToGrid":false,"NumDecimals":"0","ShowValue":true,"CustomStart":false,"NotApplicable":false,"MobileFirst":true},"QuestionDescription":"What does your free-time vs. obligations balance look like?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"&nbsp;"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":5,"Labels":{"1":{"Display":"Too Much Free-Time"},"2":{"Display":"Perfect Balance"},"3":{"Display":"Too Many Obligations"}},"QuestionID":"QID33","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID25","SecondaryAttribute":"What is the highest level of education completed by either of your parents or guardians?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What is the highest level of education completed by either of your parents or guardians?","DataExportTag":"Q20","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What is the highest level of education completed by either of your parents or guardians?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Did not finish highschool"},"2":{"Display":"High school diploma or G.E.D"},"3":{"Display":"Attended college but did not complete degree"},"4":{"Display":"Associates degree(A.A., A.S., etc.)"},"5":{"Display":"Bachelor's degree(B.A., B.S., etc.)"},"6":{"Display":"Master's degree(M.A., M.S., etc.)"},"7":{"Display":"Doctoral or professional degree(Ph.D., J.D., M.D., etc.)"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4","5","6","7"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":8,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID25","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID22","SecondaryAttribute":"What is your gender identity?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What is your gender identity?","DataExportTag":"Q17","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What is your gender identity?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Male"},"2":{"Display":"Female"},"3":{"Display":"Non-binary"},"4":{"Display":"Other","TextEntry":"true"},"5":{"Display":"Prefer not to say"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4","5"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":7,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID22","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID23","SecondaryAttribute":"What is your grade level?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What is your grade level?","DataExportTag":"Q18","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What is your grade level?","Choices":{"4":{"Display":"9"},"5":{"Display":"10"},"6":{"Display":"11"},"7":{"Display":"12"}},"ChoiceOrder":["4","5","6","7"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":8,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID23","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID32","SecondaryAttribute":"What is your level of satisfaction with the crystal sports experience?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What is your level of satisfaction with the crystal sports experience?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q2","QuestionType":"Slider","Selector":"HSLIDER","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText","CSSliderMin":0,"CSSliderMax":10,"GridLines":10,"SnapToGrid":false,"NumDecimals":"0","ShowValue":true,"CustomStart":false,"NotApplicable":false,"MobileFirst":true},"QuestionDescription":"What is your level of satisfaction with the crystal sports experience?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"&nbsp;"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":10,"Labels":{"1":{"Display":"Unsatisfied"},"2":{"Display":"Satisfied"}},"QuestionID":"QID32","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID16","SecondaryAttribute":"What is your planned major?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What is your planned major?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q16","QuestionID":"QID16","QuestionType":"TE","Selector":"SL","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What is your planned major?","Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"OFF","ForceResponseType":"RequestResponse","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":2,"NextAnswerId":1,"SearchSource":{"AllowFreeResponse":"false"},"DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID24","SecondaryAttribute":"What is your racial or ethnic identification? (select all that apply)","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What is your racial or ethnic identification? (select all that apply)","DataExportTag":"Q19","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"MAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What is your racial or ethnic identification? (select all that apply)","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"American Indian or Alaskan Native"},"2":{"Display":"Middle Eastern"},"3":{"Display":"Indian"},"4":{"Display":"Other Asian"},"6":{"Display":"Black or African American"},"7":{"Display":"Hispanic or Latino"},"8":{"Display":"Native Hawaiian or Other Pacific Islander"},"9":{"Display":"White"},"11":{"Display":"Other"},"12":{"Display":"I prefer not to respond"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4","6","7","8","9","11","12"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":14,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID24","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID12","SecondaryAttribute":"What subject assigns the most homework?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What subject assigns the most homework?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q12","QuestionType":"RO","Selector":"DND","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What subject assigns the most homework?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Math"},"2":{"Display":"Science"},"3":{"Display":"History"},"4":{"Display":"English"},"5":{"Display":"Language"},"6":{"Display":"Art"},"7":{"Display":"CADS"}},"ChoiceOrder":[1,2,3,4,5,6,7],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":8,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID12","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID35","SecondaryAttribute":"What type of Crystal events should the administration focus on improving? (Drag to rank)","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What type of Crystal events should the administration focus on improving? (Drag to rank)","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q8","QuestionType":"RO","Selector":"DND","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What type of Crystal events should the administration focus on improving? (Drag to rank)","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Arts"},"2":{"Display":"Culture\/Holidays"},"3":{"Display":"Sports"},"4":{"Display":"Dances"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":5,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID35","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID34","SecondaryAttribute":"What type of Crystal extracurriculars do you feel are most engaging? (Drag to rank)","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"What type of Crystal extracurriculars do you feel are most engaging? (Drag to rank)","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q7","QuestionType":"RO","Selector":"DND","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"What type of Crystal extracurriculars do you feel are most engaging? (Drag to rank)","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Clubs-Period Clubs"},"2":{"Display":"After School Clubs"},"3":{"Display":"Sports"},"4":{"Display":"Theater"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":5,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID34","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID18","SecondaryAttribute":"Which subject do you plan to major in?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"Which subject do you plan to major in?","DefaultChoices":false,"DataExportTag":"Q11","QuestionID":"QID18","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false},"Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"Which subject do you plan to major in?","Choices":{"4":{"Display":"STEM"},"5":{"Display":"Humanities"}},"ChoiceOrder":["4","5"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"GradingData":[],"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":7,"NextAnswerId":4}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID26","SecondaryAttribute":"With what religious affiliation do you most closely identify?","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"With what religious affiliation do you most closely identify?","DataExportTag":"Q21","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"With what religious affiliation do you most closely identify?","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Catholic"},"2":{"Display":"Orthodox(Eastern, Russian, Greek)"},"3":{"Display":"Protestant Christian"},"4":{"Display":"Other Christian(Latter Day Saints, Jehovah's Witness, etc)"},"5":{"Display":"Hindu"},"6":{"Display":"Jewish"},"7":{"Display":"Muslim"},"8":{"Display":"Sikh"},"9":{"Display":"No Religion (Atheist, Agnostic, etc)"},"11":{"Display":"Other","TextEntry":"true"},"12":{"Display":"Buddhist"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2","3","4","5","6","7","8","12","9","11"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":14,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID26","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}},{"SurveyID":"SV_3h0R382ff4LTh3g","Element":"SQ","PrimaryAttribute":"QID39","SecondaryAttribute":"Would you be interested in Crystal adding interdisciplinary electives (the history of climate cha...","TertiaryAttribute":null,"Payload":{"QuestionText":"<span
id=\"docs-internal-guid-be1d0002-7fff-8784-28df-8300e46dafd3\"><span
style=\"font-size: 11pt; font-family: Arial; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); background-color: transparent; font-variant-numeric: normal; font-variant-east-asian: normal; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;\">Would you be interested in Crystal adding interdisciplinary electives (the history of climate change, bioethics, etc)?<\/span><\/span>","DataExportTag":"Q14","QuestionType":"MC","Selector":"SAVR","SubSelector":"TX","Configuration":{"QuestionDescriptionOption":"UseText"},"QuestionDescription":"Would you be interested in Crystal adding interdisciplinary electives (the history of climate cha...","Choices":{"1":{"Display":"Yes"},"2":{"Display":"No"}},"ChoiceOrder":["1","2"],"Validation":{"Settings":{"ForceResponse":"ON","ForceResponseType":"ON","Type":"None"}},"Language":[],"NextChoiceId":4,"NextAnswerId":1,"QuestionID":"QID39","DataVisibility":{"Private":false,"Hidden":false}}}]}